<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Elearning</string>
    <string name="deskripsi">THE HAPPY PRINCE\n
High above the city, on a tall column, stood the statue of the Happy Prince. He was gilded all over with thin leaves of fine gold, for eyes he had two bright sapphires, and a large red ruby glowed on his sword-hilt.\n

He was very much admired indeed. He is as beautiful as a weathercock, remarked one of the Town Councillors who wished to gain a reputation for having artistic tastes; only not quite so useful, he added, fearing lest people should think him unpractical, which he really was not.\n

Why cant you be like the Happy Prince? asked a sensible mother of her little boy who was crying for the moon. The Happy Prince never dreams of crying for anything.\n

I am glad there is some one in the world who is quite happy, muttered a disappointed man as he gazed at the wonderful statue.\n

He looks just like an angel, said the Charity Children as they came out of the cathedral in their bright scarlet cloaks and their clean white pinafores.\n

How do you know? said the Mathematical Master, you have never seen one.\n

Ah! but we have, in our dreams, answered the children; and the Mathematical Master frowned and looked very severe, for he did not approve of children dreaming.\n

One night there flew over the city a little Swallow. His friends had gone away to Egypt six weeks before, but he had stayed behind, for he was in love with the most beautiful Reed. He had met her early in the spring as he was flying down the river after a big yellow moth, and had been so attracted by her slender waist that he had stopped to talk to her.\n

Shall I love you? said the Swallow, who liked to come to the point at once, and the Reed made him a low bow. So he flew round and round her, touching the water with his wings, and making silver ripples. This was his courtship, and it lasted all through the summer.

It is a ridiculous attachment, twittered the other Swallows; she has no money, and far too many relations; and indeed the river was quite full of Reeds. Then, when the autumn came they all flew away.\n

After they had gone he felt lonely, and began to tire of his lady- love. She has no conversation, he said, and I am afraid that she is a coquette, for she is always flirting with the wind. And certainly, whenever the wind blew, the Reed made the most graceful curtseys. I admit that she is domestic, he continued, but I love travelling, and my wife, consequently, should love travelling also."</string>
    <string name="profiletext">FARHAN ARIEF </string>
    <string name="deskripsiprofile">Tak Kenal \nMaka Tak Sayang \nIzinkan memperkenalkan diri \nFarhan Arief Nugraha kampus Pradita semester 5 yang kebetulan masuk jurusan yang cukup menguras otak dan logika yaitu pemrograman, lebih lanjut:  \n\nContact Person : 083897376513 \nEmail : furinkazan4l@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="impian">Impian atau dream lebih kita kenal dengan istilah cita-cita. Cita-cita cenderung ke profesi pekerjaan. Impian, dream, cita-cita merupakan segala bentuk harapan dan keinginan kita. \nBaik itu berupa pekerjaan/profesi, atau materil, atau yang abstrak sekalipun.
        \n Memang benar, impian dan dream itu cenderung dibicarakan oleh para pelaku bisnis MLM. Itu memotivasi mereka. Oleh karena itu, banyak di antara mereka yang berhasil di MLM, bahkan juga di profesi dan bisnis konvensional mereka. Yang tidak berhasil biasanya mereka yang tidak tekun, buru-buru berhenti, dan impiannya tidak kuat.</string>
    <string name="future">Apakah masa depan itu? Apakah masa depan benar-benar ada sehingga banyak orang bilang dan berusaha untuk meraih masa depan lebih baik?\n
Bila kita bicara dari sisi present tentang segala kejadian yang ada, maka pikiran kita hanyalah ada untuk saat ini. Artinya yang tersentuh oleh pikiran adalah saat-saat kini yang terjadi. Dalam hal inipun maka masa lalu menjadi tidak ada, ia hanya sebuah kesan dari bagian pikiran Terjebaknya manusia dalam anggapan masa lalu yang menjerat dan tidak bisa melepaskannya adalah karena ia menganggap masa lalu sebagai wujud nyata dan bukan sebagai kesan.
\nMemaknai masa lalu sebagai kesan adalah bukan menganggapnya masih sebagai wujud nyata peristiwa, namun belajar dari akibat-akibat yang ditimbulkan oleh sebab tindakan didalamnya.</string>
    <string name="sukses">Apa si sebenarnya arti sukses? Sukses adalah kemampuan untuk menjalani hidup Anda sesuai dengan keinginan Anda, melakukan apa yang yang paling dinikmati, dikelilingi oleh orang-orang Anda senangi dan hormati. Kebanyakan orang yang menganggap pengertian sukses sebagai pada saat kita wisuda, pada saat naik jabatan, atau pada saat menerima penobatan sebagai orang teladan, orang terpandai atau sejenisnya. Sukses bukan dalam pengertian seperti itu. \n
Sukses itu bukan suatu tujuan akhir dengan kualitas seadanya dan menghalalkan segala cara untuk mencapainya, tetapi sebagai suatu proses yang harus di lakukan setahap demi setahap, dan hari demi hari , bahkan menit demi menit itulah menurut pandangan saya.</string>
</resources>
